[
  {
    "question": "What Programming language is taught in introduction to programming at St John's?",
    "choice1": "Python",
    "choice2": "Java",
    "choice3": "C++",

    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What Programming language is designed for the .NET framework?",
    "choice1": "Objective-C",
    "choice2": "C",
    "choice3": "C#",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What year was Javascript Created?",
    "choice1": "1970",
    "choice2": "1990",
    "choice3": "1995",
    "answer": 3
  },

  {
    "question": "How do you print in the Console in Java?",
    "choice1": "Println",
    "choice2": "Print",
    "choice3": "Console.log",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What language does not require Semicolons",
    "choice1": "Python",
    "choice2": "Java",
    "choice3": "C#",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What OS is created by Microsoft",
    "choice1": "iOS",
    "choice2": "Windows",
    "choice3": "Linux",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a data structure",
    "choice1": "Binary-Search",
    "choice2": "Linked-List",
    "choice3": "Pyramid-Search",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What year did the C Language come out?",
    "choice1": "1965",
    "choice2": "1971",
    "choice3": "1972",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an example of a string",
    "choice1": "Hello",
    "choice2": "A",
    "choice3": "3",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an example of an integer",
    "choice1": "Hello",
    "choice2": "A",
    "choice3": "3",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an example of a double/float",
    "choice1": "Hello",
    "choice2": "A",
    "choice3": "3.14",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an example of a char",
    "choice1": "Hello",
    "choice2": "A",
    "choice3": "3",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language does not support libraries",
    "choice1": "Java",
    "choice2": "C",
    "choice3": "C++",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you use to create elements on a page in HTML?",
    "choice1": "Marks",
    "choice2": "Things",
    "choice3": "Tags",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "The rails framework pairs with which language",
    "choice1": "Ruby",
    "choice2": "Java",
    "choice3": "Python",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language is designed for Apple",
    "choice1": "Objective-C",
    "choice2": "Ruby",
    "choice3": "Swift",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the building blocks of coding using Hexadecimal code known as?",
    "choice1": "Binary",
    "choice2": "Assembly",
    "choice3": "C",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What uses bits containing 0 and 1 to communicate with the machine",
    "choice1": "Hexadecimal",
    "choice2": "Octagonal",
    "choice3": "Binary",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What do you use to Style HTML",
    "choice1": "CSS",
    "choice2": "C++",
    "choice3": "Java",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is a framework of Javascript?",
    "choice1": "Java",
    "choice2": "Kotlin",
    "choice3": "JQuery",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
